Mission: Clear up everyone's
misunderstanding about Sensei!
Starting with the bus journey.
The "Sit With Sensei" strategy!
Sensei will sit in the
seat closest to the front,
then a student will sit next to her!
It'll just be them and Sensei at first,
but I'll somehow sit
nearby to act as a go-between!
I'm not great at that kinda thing,
but I have to do it, for Sensei!
Okay, next up is Class 2,
time to get on the bus.
Sit in order of your class number,
from front to back.
Huh?! This wasn't part of the plan!
Abikura-kun, make sure you enjoy
this school camping trip too, okay?
Right...
I'm kinda happy, but...
Okay, let's regroup and
try the next strategy!
The "Soothe Sickness
with Sensei" strategy!
If Sensei tends to
someone who feels unwell,
they'll surely see that she's not scary!
Good job everyone on making
it through that long bus journey.
If anyone's feeling unwell...
Sensei?!
S-sorry.
When I got off the bus,
I was hit with a wave of nausea.
Sensei's nauseous?!
Huh? That voice was scary!!
Typical Weak and Wimpy Sensei,
she can't even handle a bus journey.
As the class president,
I'll show everyone to the
hotel in Sensei's place!
The next activity is hiking!
Encouraging each other as
we try to reach the top.
It's the perfect activity for
strengthening everyone's relationships...
but nobody's even coming near Sensei!!
She seems to be more on
edge than usual, too.
The mountains can be dangerous,
so if anything feels strange,
please let me know!
Ah, so her sense of duty is
behind that intimidating aura.
Hey, wait up.
It's dangerous to go too
far ahead of Sensei!
You should only walk as far
as our voices will carry.
Huh? W-well, you're not wrong.
B-but there's a teacher up ahead, too!
W-we'll have them supervise us!
Dammit! How can I get people
to be around Sensei...
Huh? Sensei?
Sh-she's completely exhausted!
There was no way she was gonna be able
to make it all the way up the mountain.
This plan was doomed from the start!
Ah, there you are!
Are you okay, Hiwamura-sensei?
Oh, good, Abikura's with you.
Since you have no stamina,
I planned for us to take
a break around here.
So I'll take it from here, Sensei!
S-sorry!
She lucked out in the coworker department.
I'm sorry, Abikura-kun.
I've slowed you down, too.
I'll be okay on my own,
so please go ahead and
join up with the others...
I can't just leave her
when she's struggling!
It's okay. I'm tired too,
so I'm gonna rest.
It's so hot already.
It sure is.
She's wearing some kind
of sports bra today.
A-Abikura-kun.
I'm just going to...
go over there for a moment.
Could you wait here?
Huh? Where're you going?
You probably shouldn't
go too far, you know?
Y-you're right, but...
I need to... go to the bathroom.
What?!
B-but we're still pretty
far from the lodge.
I know, that's why...
I brought a portable toilet.
So I'll just go and...
use it under that tree.
Typical Weak and Wimpy Sensei,
she even has a weak bladder.
So, um...
Could you... watch?
Watch what?!
Watch to make sure nobody comes...
Oh, right! Of course!
S-sorry.
H-how did things end up like this?
Wait, this is far worse for
her than it is for me.
I just have to guard her to the best of my
ability and make sure nobody interrupts!
I feel like I can hear a small stream.
My hiking strategy ended in failure.
The first day didn't go well at all.
And I was so busy with class president
duties that I missed the bathing time.
It's lucky the baths are still open.
The school camping trip is for
two nights and three days.
But the third day is when we travel back,
so tomorrow's basically our only chance.
How can I get Sensei to
become friends with everyone?
Yay! We've got the bath to ourselves!
The boys' bathing time and the girls'
bathing time have both finished now
so there shouldn't be anyone else here.
And it's all thanks to Yukki! Super lucky!
I thought it might be a little tough for
you to bathe with all of the other girls,
so I arranged for us to just bathe
as a smaller group with people you know.
Yeah. Thanks.
This isn't just bad,
it's a total nightmare!
I love big baths like this!
H-hey, Mizu!
You're being too loud!
I'll go and get it.
Sorry, Hiwamura.
Huh?
I got found out right away!
What're you doing here?!
W-well, one thing led to the other and...
I was late for bath time.
This is where the boys' bath is, right?
I mean, yeah,
it was until the staff cleaned it out...
I checked it was empty and then I went
and told the others they could come in.
I guess I must've come
in here during that time.
I'm sorry!
I didn't check thoroughly enough.
No, it's definitely my fault for coming in
after the designated bathing time.
Huh? Is everything okay, Hiyorin?
Wha?! E-e-everything's fine!
I-I'll figure out a way for you
to sneak out as soon as I can.
S-sorry.
The starry sky's so pretty from here!
I heard there's a legend at our school
saying that if a guy and a girl
confess their feelings to
each other under the stars
on the school camping trip,
they'll be together forever!
Totes emosh!
Really? That's cool.
So is there a guy you'd
want to be with, Mizu?
Wha?!
Wh-why're you asking me?!
Ah, I wanna know, too!
You're nice to all the guys,
so it's impossible
to tell whether you like any of ‘em, Mizu.
I-I don't really have anyone I like...
I don't!
Hey, Mizu! You're crushing Yukki!
I-I can't hear very clearly,
but it sounds like they're pretty
absorbed in their conversation.
This might be my chance...
Let's ask Hiyorin, too!
She probably knows
about real relationships!
No better time to get to know each other
then when we're sharing a bath, right?
Uh... b-but...
I-I see, Mukubayashi's trying
to help Sensei out, too.
S-so Sensei... if you don't mind...
She is scary, after all!
She scared them because she was
so busy trying to protect me!
Ah, wait... Both of you...
Look out!
A-A-A-Abikura... you jerk!
W-were the two of you... doing it?!
I brought everyone's journals.
Ah! Thanks for your hard work,
Abikura-kun.
S-Sensei, I'm really sorry about earlier.
Everything got messed up because of me.
D-don't say that! I was at fault, too.
So... what is that, exactly?
Oh, this?
I prepared all of these little props
to put in the woods
for tomorrow's test of courage!
I got them at a store,
then spiced them up
and remade a few parts..
I've spent ages getting
everything ready for tomorrow!
A-ages?!
Don't tell the others, okay?
Those are some serious props!
I was so happy with all the compliments
I got from other teachers and students
Sensei always goes all out
for her students.
when I wrote that ghost costume before.
So I thought this might be my big chance
to contribute something to the trip.
But won't this just make
everyone even more scared of you?
I thought you wanted
everyone to be able
to become friends with
you during this trip...
Yeah.
I thought it'd be nice
if I could close the distance
between us at least a little...
But right now,
the most important thing to
me as a teacher is making sure
that everyone has as much fun as
they can on this school camping trip!
So Abikura-kun,
please don't worry about me,
just do what you want to do.
Sensei...
Excuse me! I forgot a li'l something!
Oh?
Hiwamura-sensei's not here.
We just hid on impulse thinking it would
be bad to be seen together...
I wanted Hiwamura-sensei
to join in the fun!
Sh-she's so close...
She has that nice freshly-bathed smell.
A-Abikura-kun...
This feels like practice for
playing the scaring role!
She's way too excited about
the test of courage!
Only one and a half days
remaining of the camping trip.
Sensei said that the most
important thing to her
is that we all have fun on this trip,
but I can't help worrying about her.
Sensei's supervising, huh?
We'll be using fire and
knives while cooking,
so please be careful, Abikura-kun.
She's got that intimidating aura again.
My plan was to get her on good terms
with everyone by cooking together, but...
there's no way
I can invite her to join in now.
Argh!
I don't think I can cook, after all!
Nothing ever goes right for some reason.
Hey, who gave Mizu a knife?!
What's she up to?
Hiwamura.
At this rate, our group won't
get to eat any curry.
Come and help us.
But the point of this activity
is for students to build teamwork
skills and become independent.
The teachers are only
supposed to supervise.
Hiwamura...
Please?
I'll just help a little, then.
Good job, Mukubayashi, Yukishita!
They naturally found a way for
her to cook with the students!
Here!
This is my first time
seeing her in an apron.
Okay, I'll cut these
vegetables here, then.
Thanks.
Ah. I-I kinda have a
bad feeling about this.
Oh no!
Is she putting a curse on the food?!
Will we die if we eat it?!
Typical Weak and Wimpy Sensei,
even her knife skills are lacking!
This can't be good!
They're going to get the
wrong idea about her again!
M-man! Hiwamura-sensei has
such delicate arms, you see!
Right, Mukubayashi?
Huh? Really?
Huh? What're you talking
about all of a sudden?
Gross.
Th-this idiot!
Thanks to that idiot Mukubayashi,
I cut my finger.
O-oh no!
What?!
Uhh... Sensei?!
S-sowwy!
When I used to get hurt,
my mom always did this for me,
so I just did it without thinking!
Weak n' Wimpy's mom sure is old-school!
I'm sorry,
that was inappropriate.
Let's go and disinfect it.
It-it's fine.
Was she... eating Abikura's finger?!
Is he offering his own flesh
and blood as a sacrifice?!
And so, everybody kept saying the curry
that night was "Abikura" flavored...
Aw, darn.
It started raining all of a sudden.
Huh? The test of courage
is gonna be cancelled?!
I was looking forward to that!
We should just use
umbrellas and do it anyway!
And we have a study period instead...
Why'd it have to happen
on our school camping trip?
This is the worst!
Um, Sensei!
Abikura-kun.
Is the test of courage really cancelled?
After you worked so hard getting
everything ready...
Yes... I'm really sorry.
I totally jinxed it.
Whenever I have an important event,
it'll always rain.
It rained the day of my
employment exam, too.
So this is probably my fault.
Aw, come on.
You can't blame yourself
for the weather, Sensei!
S-sorry. I didn't mean to lose my cool.
Everyone has about two
hours of free time now,
and then we have a study period.
Don't be late, okay?
H-Hiwamura-sensei!
Come with me for a moment!
Students from class 2 have taken
over an entire floor of the facility!
Whoa!
This is amazing!
Come on in, everyone!
Look!
Wow, that looks fun!
It's so elaborate!
I wonder who made all of these props?
What... is all of this?
Ah, Hiyorin! Check it out!
We made an indoor test of courage!
Isn't it awesome?!
We used this whole floor!
There are monsters hidden in each room,
and you have to collect the talismans
and get to the goal over there!
It's pretty scary,
since it looks like a school at night.
Thanks to all the props you made, Hiyorin,
it's super immersive
and everybody loves it!
Abikura suddenly had this idea to
get around the bad weather.
A-Abikura-kun came up with this?!
There wasn't much time,
but he asked all of us
to help set it all up.
At first the teacher in charge said we
couldn't do it since it wasn't scheduled,
but Abikura managed to convince him and we
got permission from the facility to do it!
Everyone's... smiling.
I-I'm so happy!
H-Hiyorin!
I felt so bad for everyone that we
couldn't do the test of courage...
since it was the last activity
of the school camping trip.
I hated seeing the
sad looks on their faces.
Mukubayashi-san! Are you having fun?
You bet! It's like Halloween, it's ace!
How about you, Yukishita-san?
It's all right.
I'm glad to hear it! What a relief!
I-I'm wiped out.
Why'd I have to write some
letter of apology kinda thing?
Oh, you're back.
S-Sensei!
Abikura-kun!
I'm sorry for doing
all this without asking!
I was just thinking of getting
you to come and check it out!
Look!
Please go and scare people
to your heart's content!
That day, plenty of
students played a monster,
but Sensei was the scariest of them all.
Hey, did you hear?
Apparently Spooky Scary Sensei was the one
who made all of those props for today,
and prepared everything
for the test of courage.
Whoa, seriously?
That's a perfect fit for her.
But, you know...
that must mean she's
not a bad teacher after all.
Oh, it's stopped raining.
What's happening here?
Sensei called me out here,
but something seems strange.
W-was I a little too pushy?
A-Abikura-kun.
Thank you!
I heard that you took the lead in
planning the indoor test of courage.
I had completely given up,
so it didn't even occur to
me that we could hold it inside.
Everyone had fun tonight
thanks to you, Abikura-kun.
Well, I just arranged the props you made
and brought in some people to help.
I couldn't have done anything
without your hard work.
That's why I'm convinced that the
reason everyone had such a great time
was because you wanted us to enjoy
this school camping trip, Sensei.
But although I wanted Sensei to get closer
to all of the students on this trip,
I had to give up on that in favor of the
preparations for the test of courage.
Since I knew that wasn't what
she really wanted, anyways.
But... aren't you putting
undue stress on yourself?
You only became the class president
for the first time this year.
And before that,
you weren't the type of student
to be so proactive, right?
Your previous homeroom teacher and
Mukubayashi-san said as much.
R-right...
It's true that,
looking back on it,
this school camping trip was
anything but uncomplicated.
Well, that's just how much...
I like you, Sensei.
Ah, I mean, uh... as a teacher!
Wh-wh-what am I saying?!
I respect you, as an educator!
D-do you really?
I-I can't believe it...
even though I'm only a first year teacher,
getting a compliment like that...
This is so unexpected!
Wh-what a relief.
She doesn't seem to suspect
that I meant it romantically.
Y-you overestimate me!
You shouldn't respect a
greenhorn like me this much!
Ah, but... i-it makes
me r-r-r-really happy!
She's so thrilled!
W-well, it's great that
everyone had so much fun!
And no one got hurt,
so I'd say this school
camping trip was a big success!
D-did you have fun, Abikura-kun?
Was it a good trip for you?
Me? Of course.
It was certainly eventful,
and I did lots of new things,
but this is probably the most
fun I've had at a school event.
I'm so glad.
I also...
like you too, Abikura-kun!
Guess you and I have a mutual fondness for
each other as teacher and student, huh?
S-s-s-s-she only meant it in that sense?!
W-well, you see, Sensei....
S-s-s-s-sorry! The ground's all muddy!
You're the one tripping on
me for once, Abikura-kun.
My not-at-all uncomplicated school
camping trip ended with Sensei's smile.
School camping trip,
day one!
Lesson 4
A Weak and Wimpy School Camp
Clench
Student Number: 1
Sit With Sensei strategy:
Failure
Twitch
Soothe Sickness with
Sensei strategy:
Failure
Shake
Twitch
Squeeze
Blush
Ba-dump
Squeeze
Loom
Whump
Teaching staff 3
Ba-dump
Excited
School camping trip,
day 2
Shake
Loom
Tug
Uwu
Ba-dump
Shing
Shake
Slice
Nom
Gasp
Ba-dump
Orientation room
Indoor
Test of Courage
Eeeeek!
Ba-dump
Glow
Shine
Fwump
 